<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Food Paradise</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="openDrawer">open_drawer</string>
    <string name="closeDrawer">close_drawer</string>
    <string name="privacyinfo">Food Paradise Private Limited(Formerly known as Food Paradise
        Media Private Limited) and/or its affiliates respect your privacy and is committed to
        protecting it through its compliance with its privacy policies. This policy describes: the
        types of information that Food Paradise may collect from you when you access or use its websites,
        applications and other online services (collectively, referred as Services); and its practices for
        collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.Your data controller is
        responsible for the collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information
        in accordance with its privacy standards as well as any applicable national laws. Your data controller may
        transfer data to other members of Food Paradise as described in this Privacy Policy. Food Paradise may process
        and retain your personal information on its servers in India where its data centers are located, and/or on the servers
        of its third parties (in or outside India), having contractual relationships with Food Paradise. This policy may change
        from time to time, your continued use of Food Paradise\'s Services after it makes any change is deemed to be acceptance
        of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.</string>
    <string name="aboutinfo">It’s been called a “truly grand restaurant” and “a work of
        art in its own right,” a restaurant “on the forefront of the Paradise cuisine revolution”
        where “true culinary artistry is a constant.”For more than 40 years The Food Paradise Restaurant
        has been all that, putting Kansas City on the nation’s culinary map and introducing local fine dining
        fans to some of the country’s most celebrated chefs. That, The Paradise most certainly has been, and
        continues to be. The Paradise continues to be that place. The spectacular setting and view remain. Guest
        chefs still share their culinary gifts in one-time-only events. Fundraising galas still support worthy causes.
        Private wedding receptions, retirement parties and family reunions continue, and the public is welcomed for holiday
        celebrations. Once again, Adele Hall said it best.</string>

</resources>